graphicdesignblender.com 2014-06-04

# Privacy Policy | Graphic Design Blender

This site collects and uses your information in various ways and  _always_ keeps that information private. We’ll never share your private information, sell your information, or otherwise exploit your info for purposes other than to add value to your design business.

## Wondering if you should sign up for the email newsletter?

Here’s what we **WILL  **do with your email address:

  * We will send you emails multiple times each week stuffed full of helpful information on building and growing your design business.
  * We will send you special offers on our ebooks (sometimes even free ebooks) and other cool deals and offers we learn about or run ourselves. These are very rare.
  * We  _may_ use your email address to connect with you on facebook in order to send you reminders about content, promotions, etc.
  * We  _may_ use your email to just reach out now and again and say “hey, you’re awesome. Thanks for subscribing.”

Here’s what we **WON’T** do with your email address:

  *  **We won’t send you spam.** We get tons of people begging us to send you garbage for a hefty check. But we won’t ever do it. You’ll only get relevant, quality, pre-approved content from this blog in your inbox.
  *  **We won’t sell or rent your information.  **The only place your email will ever be stored is inside our list management system inside of MailChimp (our email list service provider). We won’t export the list to sell or rent to third parties.
  *  **We won’t abuse your trust.  **We know it can be a big deal to hand over your email. We respect that. We’ll never abuse that. You have our word.

## More Privacy Info

 **What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy..

 **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

• To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

• To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

• To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)  
•; To process transactions

> Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

• To send periodic emails

> The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

 **How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

 **Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and keep track of advertisements and .

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

 **Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

 **Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

 **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [websites privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

 **Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

http://www.graphicdesignblender.com/contact

P.O. Box 160243  
Clearfield, Utah 84016  
United States
